const gradepre2data=[
    {
        question:"ability",
        choices:["安定性","能力","柔軟性","耐久性"],
        answer:1
    },
    {
        question:"behavior",
        choices:["行動","労働","活力","勇気"],
        answer:0
    },
    {
        question:"chemistry",
        choices:["化学","科学","理科","実験"],
        answer:0
    },
    {
        question:"explanation",
        choices:["探検","期待","説明","試験"],
        answer:2
    },
    {
        question:"organization",
        choices:["臓器","有機物","組織","オルガン奏者"],
        answer:2
    },
    {
        question:"look up",
        choices:["調べる","見つめる","世話をする","尊敬する"],
        answer:0
    },
    {
        question:"break down",
        choices:["別れる","勃発する","故障する","侵入する"],
        answer:2
    },
    {
        question:"fill out",
        choices:["排出する","記入する","代わりをする","漏れる"],
        answer:1
    },
    {
        question:"put off",
        choices:["延期する","脱ぐ","片付ける","解雇する"],
        answer:0
    },
    {
        question:"carry out",
        choices:["成功する","持ち運ぶ","伝える","実行する"],
        answer:3
    }
]

export default gradepre2data;